[{"success": true, "timeout": false, "failed_images": [], "failed_audio": [], "failed_video": [], "trial_type": "preload", "trial_index": 0, "time_elapsed": 327, "internal_node_id": "0.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 7392, "stimulus": ["<p> Welcome! </p> <p> We are conducting an experiment about how people evaluate intuitive physics situations when asked a question in plain english. Your answers will be used to inform computer science and cognitive science research.</p><p> This experiment should take no more than <strong>10 minutes</strong></p> <p> We take your time seriously! The email for the main experimenter is <strong>juliush@mit.edu</strong>. </br></br> Please write this down now, and email us with the subject line <i>Human experiment for intuitive physics</i> if you have problems submitting this task, or if it takes much more time than expected. </p><p>  Press any key to begin. </p>"], "response": "k", "trial_type": "html-keyboard-response", "trial_index": 1, "time_elapsed": 7720, "internal_node_id": "0.0-1.0"}, {"rt": 32932, "stimulus": ["<p>In this experiment, you will be presented with a series of images containing <strong>stacks of blocks and some simple questions.</strong></p><p>The block are stacked on a grey platform in a configuration which may or may not be stable.</p><p>In each situation, you will be asked to imagine what will occur after a sufficiently large amount of time has passed and gravity has finished acting on the stacks of blocks.", "<p>Your task will be to think about how these blocks will fall and their position <strong>after they have finished falling</strong>. Note that sometimes, you may be presented with a stable stack where no blocks will fall.<p>You will enter your answer for each question by clicking a rating on a <strong>7-point multiple choice scale</strong> ranging from <strong>1 (definitely no)</strong> to <strong>7 (definitely yes)</strong>.", "<p>You will see descriptions of <strong>24  different scenarios</strong> in total.</p><p> When you are ready, please click any key to complete a quick comprehension check, before moving on to the experiment. </p>"], "response": "k", "trial_type": "html-keyboard-response", "trial_index": 2, "time_elapsed": 40654, "internal_node_id": "0.0-2.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 18480, "response": {"Q0": "Look at images containing blocks and answer questions about what will happen in the image after gravity has acted on the blocks.", "Q1": "By selecting an option from a multiple choice scale."}, "question_order": [0, 1], "trial_type": "survey-multi-choice", "trial_index": 3, "time_elapsed": 59139, "internal_node_id": "0.0-2.0-1.0"}, {"rt": 31667, "response": {"Q0": 5}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will most of the blocks have stayed on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "1", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "9", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 4, "time_elapsed": 90814, "internal_node_id": "0.0-3.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 17870, "response": {"Q0": 5}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the majority of the large blocks be on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "0", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "6", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 5, "time_elapsed": 108689, "internal_node_id": "0.0-4.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 16108, "response": {"Q0": 5}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any red blocks remaining on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "5", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "31", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 6, "time_elapsed": 124806, "internal_node_id": "0.0-5.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 20495, "response": {"Q0": 6}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the majority of the large blocks be on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "4", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "30", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 7, "time_elapsed": 145304, "internal_node_id": "0.0-6.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 23648, "response": {"Q0": 1}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be more red blocks to the left of the platform than purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "3", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "20", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 8, "time_elapsed": 168961, "internal_node_id": "0.0-7.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 11145, "response": {"Q0": 5}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will most of the blocks have stayed on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "0", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "3", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 9, "time_elapsed": 180112, "internal_node_id": "0.0-8.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 31014, "response": {"Q0": 1}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the number of blocks on the platform be divisible by 3?", "box_ensemble_index": "2", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "17", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 10, "time_elapsed": 211132, "internal_node_id": "0.0-9.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 11051, "response": {"Q0": 1}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will most of the blocks have stayed on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "6", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "39", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 11, "time_elapsed": 222193, "internal_node_id": "0.0-10.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 8878, "response": {"Q0": 5}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "4", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "28", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 12, "time_elapsed": 231078, "internal_node_id": "0.0-11.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 11824, "response": {"Q0": 5}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be more red blocks to the left of the platform than purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "6", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "38", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 13, "time_elapsed": 242908, "internal_node_id": "0.0-12.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 7638, "response": {"Q0": 5}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will most of the blocks have stayed on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "3", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "21", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 14, "time_elapsed": 250551, "internal_node_id": "0.0-13.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 10452, "response": {"Q0": 4}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will most of the blocks have stayed on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "5", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "33", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 15, "time_elapsed": 261013, "internal_node_id": "0.0-14.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 11143, "response": {"Q0": 5}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will most of the blocks have stayed on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "4", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "27", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 16, "time_elapsed": 272161, "internal_node_id": "0.0-15.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 11450, "response": {"Q0": 0}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the number of blocks on the platform be divisible by 3?", "box_ensemble_index": "4", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "29", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 17, "time_elapsed": 283618, "internal_node_id": "0.0-16.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 27506, "response": {"Q0": 1}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the number of blocks on the platform be divisible by 3?", "box_ensemble_index": "1", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "11", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 18, "time_elapsed": 311132, "internal_node_id": "0.0-17.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 12208, "response": {"Q0": 5}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "5", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "34", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 19, "time_elapsed": 323351, "internal_node_id": "0.0-18.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 7964, "response": {"Q0": 6}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the majority of the large blocks be on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "7", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "48", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 20, "time_elapsed": 331324, "internal_node_id": "0.0-19.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 5993, "response": {"Q0": 0}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "3", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "22", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 21, "time_elapsed": 337327, "internal_node_id": "0.0-20.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 12375, "response": {"Q0": 1}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will most of the blocks have stayed on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "2", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "15", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 22, "time_elapsed": 349711, "internal_node_id": "0.0-21.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 7588, "response": {"Q0": 0}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the number of blocks on the platform be divisible by 3?", "box_ensemble_index": "3", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "23", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 23, "time_elapsed": 357311, "internal_node_id": "0.0-22.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 7189, "response": {"Q0": 5}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any red blocks remaining on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "7", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "43", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 24, "time_elapsed": 364516, "internal_node_id": "0.0-23.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 13743, "response": {"Q0": 3}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be more red blocks to the left of the platform than purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "5", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "32", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 25, "time_elapsed": 378273, "internal_node_id": "0.0-24.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 6847, "response": {"Q0": 1}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any red blocks remaining on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "1", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "7", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 26, "time_elapsed": 385132, "internal_node_id": "0.0-25.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 7793, "response": {"Q0": 5}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any red blocks remaining on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "4", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "25", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 27, "time_elapsed": 392931, "internal_node_id": "0.0-26.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 28887, "response": {"Q0": "9", "Q1": "8", "Q2": "No. ", "Q3": "This was a fun experiment!\n"}, "trial_type": "survey-text", "trial_index": 28, "time_elapsed": 421835, "internal_node_id": "0.0-27.0"}]